We are free
May we always be so,
may we always be so
And let the lights be denied before,
the lights,
the lights
of the Sun
before we break the solemn vow
which the Fatherland elevated to the Eternal
which the Fatherland elevated to the Eternal.
On its summits may the Andes sustain
the two-color flag or standard,
may it announce to the centuries the effort
that being free,
that being free gave us forever.
Under its shadow may we live calmly,
and, at birth of the sun in its summits,
may we all renew the great oath
that we rendered,
that we rendered to the God of Jacob,
to the God of Jacob...
We are free
May we always be so,
may we always be so
And let the lights be denied before,
the lights,
the lights
of the Sun
before we break the solemn vow
which the Fatherland elevated to the Eternal
Before we break the solemn vow
which the Fatherland elevated to the Eternal.